Heyner Cuevas

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO

Phone: (+33) 7 74 16 48 49 Email: heyner128@gmail.com Github: github.com/heyner128

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/heyner-cuevas

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a software developer with three years of experience designing, coding an testing solutions for the manufacturing industry using Java and React. Engaged with the quality and the continuous learning of new technologies and working methodologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Consulting Software Developper

SKF France | Feb 2022 - Dec 2024

- · Development of a website to manage bearing packaging orders.
- Development of an API for managing production reference information.
- Design of unit and integration test.
- · Workflow and data processing automation.

Technical Stack: Spring, Java, Javascript, React, Git, Azure DevOps, JUnit, Jest, Power BI

Software Development Intern

SKF France | Sept 2021 - Dec 2021

- Development of a database and a graphical interface for quality data management.
- Development of dashboards and data visualizations.
- Documentation, support and maintenance of the developed applications.

Technical Stack: Spring, Java, Javascript, Git, Power BI

EDUCATION

INSA Centre Val de Loire

Masters degree | Sep 2019 - Nov 2021 Masters in Industrial Engineering

 Specialization in Performance and Reliability of industrial systems

National University of Colombia

Bachelors degree | Feb 2013 - Nov 2021 BS in industrial engineering

HARD-SKILLS

API development
Automated testing
OOP patterns
Agile Methodology
Database Modelling

SOFT-SKILLS

Adaptability Curiosity Problem-solving Self-motivation